Guide to the Alan Sondheim Papers MSS.267
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I. Written Work
  - "Current Condition of the Screen.txt Saved in the C:\Dos\What.txt After Return Through Inadvertent and Unsolicited Reiteration of an Originary Imaginary Trace", 1994 (Box 34, Folder 31)
  - "Current Sound Texts," Alan Sondheim With Devonna Walker, Voice, Undated (Box 34, Folder 32)
  - "Cut", Undated (Box 34, Folder 33)
  - "Cut Desert", 1994 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - "Cybermidrash", 2003 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_5)
    "Cybermidrash" is a collborative multimedia web project between Alan Sondheim and Joel Weishaus.
  - "Cybermind" Email Listserv, 1994-2000 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_6, Box 35, Folder 2)
  - "Da Da", Undated (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - "Dali", Undated (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - "Damaged Life", Undated (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - "Damaged Life. Liner Notes", Undated (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - "Dance", Undated (Box 35, Folder 7, 8, 9, 10)
  - "Dance Description", 1971 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - "Dark Blue of the Air", Undated (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - "Dawn" by Reiner Strasser and Alan Sondheim, 2005 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_7)
    "Dawn" is a multimedia project by Alan Sondheim and Reiner Strasser. Text, photography, and sound is by Alan Sondheim. Musical compositions are composed by Reiner Strasser.
  - "Dawns", Undated (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - "De- ii, i, I, Ø", Undated (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - "Dead End", Undated (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - "Dead Time: The Machinery of Reality", 1981 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - "Death", Undated (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - "Death and Computation", Undated (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - "The Death Car the Suicide", Undated (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - "The Death of American Art," Art and Artists, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - "Death of Gender", Undated (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - "The Death of Henry Ward Beecher", 1968 (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - "Death of Logic, Logical Death", Undated (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - "The Death of Sean Smith", Undated (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - "Death Row Death Row", Undated (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - "Death/Sentencing", 1985 (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - "Death Sex; Sex Death", Undated (Box 35, Folder 27)
  - "Debrisfilm", Undated (Box 35, Folder 28)
  - "Decadence", Undated (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - "Decomposition: The Transamerican Avant-Garde," Art Papers, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 30)
  - "Deleuze" Email Listserv, 1994 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_8)
  - "Delusion in the Form of a Preface", Undated (Box 35, Folder 31)
  - "The Departure of Cinema: Treatment", Undated (Box 35, Folder 32)
  - "Deprivation", Undated (Box 35, Folder 33)
  - "Description of a Film", Undated (Box 35, Folder 34)
  - "The Description of the History of Measurement and Substance", Undated (Box 35, Folder 35)
  - "Des Esseintes", Undated (Box 35, Folder 36)
  - "Des Esseintes and Decadence (Con't.)", Undated (Box 35, Folder 37)
  - "Development of a Generalized Structure Applicable to the Foundations of Most Disciplines," Meta Ltd., Undated (Box 35, Folder 38)
  - "Diary Which is Not a Diary in Continuation", Undated (Box 35, Folder 39)
  - "Differance", Undated (Box 35, Folder 40)
  - "Discourse on the Civilized", 1975 (Box 35, Folder 41)
  - Disorders of the Real, 1985-1989 (Box 35, Folder 42)
  - Disorders of the Real, 1987 (Box 35, Folder 43)
  - Disorders of the Real: Abstract, 1982 (Box 35, Folder 44)
  - "Distinction", Undated (Box 35, Folder 45)
  - "Documents Relating to the Lectures in Denmark", 1973 (Box 35, Folder 46)
  - "Done For!", Undated (Box 35, Folder 47)
  - "The Doom Mummy" by William Louis Sørensen, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 48)
  - "Double", Undated (Box 35, Folder 49)
  - "Dream", Undated (Box 35, Folder 50)
  - "The Dream of All of You", Undated (Box 35, Folder 51)
  - "DRG.TXT", Undated (Box 35, Folder 52)
  - "Dusks", Undated (Box 35, Folder 53)
  - "E.A.T.", 1983 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - "Economy of Dreams", Undated (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - "Ecriture and Others: Some Writings", 1970-1980 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - "Electronic Music in Concert" by Laura E. Hersh, Brown Daily Herald, April 1968 (Box 77, Folder 28)
  - "Electronic Subjectivity", Undated (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - "Eleven Piece Series", Undated (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - "Ellipse Injection Into Active Visual Field: Stages", 1971 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - "El Oud", Undated (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Email and Online Chat Correspondence, 1994-2009 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_28)
  - "Em/bedded", Undated (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - "Employment", Undated (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - "The Empress/The Retinue", Undated (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - "Engage", 1973 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - "The Enterprise of the Colonels", Undated (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - "The Enterprising Florist", Undated (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - "Errata to The Structure of Reality", Undated (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - "The Establishment of Human Positioning," Meta Ltd., Undated (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - "Etc.", Undated (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - "Eternal Terminological Return", 1987-1989 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - "Etiquette/Perversion", Undated (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - "Event", Undated (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - "The Event of Your Life. The Event of a Life.", Undated (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - "Everything", Undated (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - "Evocation of the Former Familiar", Undated (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - "Exhaustion of Gender at the Foot of the Hermaphrodite", Undated (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - Exhibit Essays by Alan Sondheim for Connie Bostic and George Stone, 1988 (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - "Exhibition", Undated (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - "The Exhibition of the Fissured Terrain", Undated (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - "Exhibitionism", Undated (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - "Exile and Others", 1980 (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - "The Expansion of a Point Source", Undated (Box 36, Folder 29)
  - "Experimental Writing", Undated (Box 36, Folder 30)
  - "Factory/Craft/'Art' ", Undated (Box 36, Folder 31)
  - "Failure, Ideology, and the World Order: Representative Statements", Undated (Box 36, Folder 32)
  - "Familiarity: Family, Art, and Ideology" by Laura Hayes and Alan Sondheim, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 33)
  - "Fantasies…", Undated (Box 36, Folder 34)
  - Fantasms of the Real, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 35)
  - "Far Hills Project", Undated (Box 36, Folder 36)
  - "Fashion", Undated (Box 36, Folder 37)
  - "February 8, 3:00 A.M. 2200", 1988 (Box 36, Folder 38)
  - "Feer", Undated (Box 36, Folder 39)
  - Fever (Fantasms of the Real), 1989 (Box 37, Folder 1, 2)
  - "Few Tired Lines on the Same Subject", 1985 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - "Fibre Bundle", Undated (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - "Fiction of Philosophy" Email Listserv, 1994-2000 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_9)
  - "Figure", Undated (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - "File: Compute", Undated (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - "File: Exper", Undated (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - "File: Iceland", Undated (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - "File: New", Undated (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - "File: One", Undated (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - "File: Store", Undated (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - "File: Store.Text", Undated (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - "File: System.Wrk.Text", 1979 (Box 38, Folder 11, 12)
  - "File: Three", Undated (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - "File: Two", Undated (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - "Film", Undated (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - "Film", 1983 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - "Film and Video", Undated (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - "Film Clara", Undated (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - "Film Clusters", Undated (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - "Film for Characters", Undated (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - "The Film in Which I Am Lost", 1984 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - "Film of Weeds and Directions", Undated (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - "Filmscript", Undated (Box 38, Folder 23, 24)
  - "Filmscript for Denise", Undated (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - "Filmscript: Question and Answer (Period)", Undated (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - "Filmscript: (Smoky Mountains)", Undated (Box 38, Folder 27)
  - "The Film Sleazy", Undated (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - "Film, Theatre, Theater", Undated (Box 38, Folder 29)
  - "Film, Video, and Photography: A Series of Statements", Undated (Box 38, Folder 30)
  - "The First Day of the Smog Alert Everyone Went to Town", Undated (Box 38, Folder 31)
  - "Fissure (Your Voice, Adjacent, Absent)", Undated (Box 38, Folder 32)
  - "Five Texts", 1976-1977 (Box 38, Folder 33)
  - "Flight", Undated (Box 38, Folder 34)
  - "Flow, Etc.", Undated (Box 38, Folder 35)
  - "Flying", Undated (Box 38, Folder 36)
  - "Fool of Philosophy", Undated (Box 38, Folder 37)
  - "Footnote: Dust on the Print", Undated (Box 38, Folder 38)
  - "For Al Wilson, Member of Canned Heat, Friend, Guitar Teacher, Who Died a While Back", Undated (Box 38, Folder 39)
  - "Force and Speaking for Oneself", Undated (Box 38, Folder 40)
  - "The Foreplay of Identity", Undated (Box 38, Folder 41)
  - "Forgery", Undated (Box 38, Folder 42)
  - "Found Poem", Undated (Box 38, Folder 43)
  - "Foundation of Linguistics", Undated (Box 38, Folder 44)
  - "Four Plays", 1967 (Box 38, Folder 45)
  - "Four Writings in One Writing", Undated (Box 38, Folder 46)
  - "Fragment Bomb Wind," Parallax, 2000 (Box 38, Folder 47)
  - "Fragment: Death Cry", Undated (Box 38, Folder 48)
  - "Fragments", Undated (Box 38, Folder 49)
  - "From a Play: Childpoem I", Undated (Box 38, Folder 50)
  - "From: A Series of Statements as if They Were Absent from a Lecture", Undated (Box 38, Folder 51)
  - "From Poem Hours", 1969 (Box 38, Folder 52)
  - "From Modernity to Postmodernity", Undated (Box 38, Folder 53)
  - "From Rafael Alberti: 'Si Mi Voz Muriera en Tierra' ", Undated (Box 38, Folder 54)
  - "Fucked Up, Thrown in Jail, in the Country of the Secret Police", Undated (Box 38, Folder 55)
  - "The Function of the Avant-Garde: Possibilities", Undated (Box 38, Folder 56)
  - "The Fundamental Rule in the Structure of Reality", Undated (Box 38, Folder 57)
  - "The Future, Speaking Of or About", Undated (Box 38, Folder 58)
  - "Gas Chamber", Undated (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - "The Genaeology of Machines", Undated (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - "General Conjecture", Undated (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - "General Description of the World," Meta, Ltd., 1972 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - "General Scheme", Undated (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - General Theory - First Draft, 1974 (Box 39, Folder 6, 7, Box 56, Folder 1)
  - "Geography Now and Then", 1988 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - "Germs and Peaches", Undated (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - "GGJ", Undated (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - "The Gift", Undated (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - "The Girl in Red and the Girl in Brown", Undated (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - "Gnosticism", Undated (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - "God", Undated (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - "Gome Performance", Undated (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - "Graham, Science, And Philosophy in the Soviet Union", Undated (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - "The Graph", Undated (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - "Graphemic Content of the English Language", Undated (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - "The Graphic Representation of the Sine Function, with 1/2x Reductions, Frame by Frame", Undated (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - "Grasp", 1983 (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - "The Grasping of the Most Elementary", Undated (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - "Grounds for a Procedural Semiotics: Calculator Programming and an Outline of an Analysis of Marxism in Relation to 'The Structure of Reality' ", 1978 (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - "Group Consensus in the Production of Literary Works", Undated (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - "Gulliver", 1975 (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - "Ha-Ha", Undated (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - "Halwell's", Undated (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - "Hands", Undated (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Hazen/Pueblo Notebook, Undated (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - "Henderson Awake", Undated (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - "He Pearls That We", 2007 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - "Her Death", Undated (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - "Here and There", 1979 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - "Heroes, How They File Past", Undated (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - "Hiatus: Neutralization and Naïve Ratiocination", Undated (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - "Hideout Work Script Notes", Undated (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - "Hierarchical Structuring," Meta Ltd., Undated (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - "The Hierarchy of Entropies", Undated (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - "His Time", Undated (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - "History (A Meditation)", 1985 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - "History and Cancellation: The Pool at the Heart of the World", Undated (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - "History is a Condition of the Present, Not of the Past", Undated (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - "The History of Film", Undated (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - "Hollywood and Infinity", Undated (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - "Holly Would", Undated (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - "Holocaust: Representation as EMISSION Within Negative Cultural Space", Undated (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - "Hospital Comments", 1963 (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - "The Hour of the Zeros", Undated (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - "How I Write", Undated (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - "How to Disappear", Undated (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - "Hymn, Home, and the End of the World: Script", 1984 (Box 40, Folder 26)
  - "I", Undated (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - "I Am A Woman", Undated (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - "Icelandic Program", Undated (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - "Idaho", Undated (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - "The Idea of Switzerland in Lambdamoo", 1994 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - "Ideas on Time: Addenda to 'A Series of Works Leading…' ", Undated (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - "Ideal Realities," The Soho Weekly News, November 25 1976 (Box 77, Folder 24)
  - "The Ideological Machine", Undated (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - "The Ideological Enterprise", Undated (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - "I Die! I Faint! I Fail!", Undated (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - "I Don't Ask Sympathy For This", Undated (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - "I Have Watched…", Undated (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - "The Illuminated Countryside", 1969-1975 (Box 41, Folder 12, 13, 14)
  - "The Image/Representation", Undated (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - "Imagine", Undated (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - "I Model; You Take My Picture," CEPA Journal, 1988 (Box 41, Folder 17, 18)
  - "Implications", Undated (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - "Improvisations on the Human Element", Undated (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - "Incendiary Device Text", 1990 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - "Incorrect: Final Fire of the Video World", 2002 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - "The Increasing Blankness of Consumer Goods", Undated (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - "Increasingly My Life Turns Toward Violent Imbrication", Undated (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - "In Defense of (Linguistic) Obscurity", 1985 (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - "Indexicality", Undated (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - "Individuals", 1973 (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - "Inertia", Undated (Box 41, Folder 28)
  - "In Lieu of", 1977 (Box 41, Folder 29)
  - "In Lieu of the Process (Napoleon)", Undated (Box 41, Folder 30)
  - "In Praise of Miro's 'Still Life With Old Shoe' ", Undated (Box 41, Folder 31)
  - "Inquisition: The Judgement of Art", Undated (Box 41, Folder 32)
  - "Inscription", Undated (Box 41, Folder 33)
  - "Inscription Divisibility", Undated (Box 41, Folder 34)
  - "Inscription Types", Undated (Box 41, Folder 35)
  - "Instrumentality", Undated (Box 41, Folder 36)
  - "Interface", Undated (Box 41, Folder 37)
  - "Interim Report on Recent Work," Meta Ltd., 1973 (Box 41, Folder 38)
  - "Internal Exile", 1985 (Box 41, Folder 39)
  - Internet Text, 1994-2006 (Box 41, Folder 40)
  - Internet Text, 1994-2006 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_29)
    "Internet Text" is an twelve year project in which Alan Sondheim posted textual works online. He describes it as a "long-standing online performance that interrogates the nature of computer-mediated consciousness and digital textuality."
  - "The Interpretation of Dreams", Undated (Box 41, Folder 41)
  - "Interrogation", Undated (Box 41, Folder 42)
  - "Interruption Piece", Undated (Box 41, Folder 43)
  - "Interview", Undated (Box 41, Folder 44)
  - "In the 3rd World" by Alan Sondheim and Allison Ritch, 1982 (Box 41, Folder 45)
  - "(In These Woods, You Can't Go Home Again…)", 1977 (Box 41, Folder 46)
  - "Interview with Jerry Cullum," Art Papers, 1988 (Box 41, Folder 47)
  - "Introduction", Undated (Box 41, Folder 48)
  - "Introduction", 1984 (Box 41, Folder 49)
  - "Introduction to the Writing", Undated (Box 41, Folder 50)
  - "The Intransigent Divisions", Undated (Box 41, Folder 51)
  - "Intransigent Projections", Undated (Box 41, Folder 52)
  - "Invasion of the Feminine", Undated (Box 41, Folder 53)
  - "Inventories", Undated (Box 41, Folder 54)
  - "Invisible Children", Undated (Box 41, Folder 55)
  - "I See My Films in the Following Manner", Undated (Box 41, Folder 56)
  - "Is Perfection An Attribute or an Absence of Attributes", Undated (Box 41, Folder 57)
  - "I Tell a Story", Undated (Box 41, Folder 58)
  - "It's Been Said", Undated (Box 41, Folder 59)
  - "I Want to Be a Woman", 1985 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - "I Want to Fuck You", Undated (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - "I Want to Report How I Found the World" Notebook, Undated (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - "I Went to the Movies", 1983 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - "Jabès", Undated (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - "The Jackson Pollock Essay," Art Papers, 1985 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - "Jennifer", 1998 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - "Jennifer in Phaedra," Backwoods Chaplet Series No. 43, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Jennifer, Julu, and Nikuko, 1997-2000 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_30)
    Jennifer, Julu, and Nikuko are personas or "avatars" through which Alan Sondheim expresses himself.
  - "Jerusalem", 1963 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - "Jerusalem: An Exercise", Undated (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - "Joel", Undated (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - "Journal", Undated (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - "Journal (Volume VIII)", 1975 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - "Juarez: The Digital Domain/The Bruise", 2004 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - "Judean Hills", Undated (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - "Just Gaming", Undated (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - "The Kantian Landscape", Undated (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - "Keene", Undated (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - "Kitty", Undated (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - "Knowledge Flux," Perforations 3, 1992 (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - "Köld RaÞ Undan Hverju Rifi (Cold Counsels From Every Rib)", Undated (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - "Kudzu", Undated (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - "Kudzu," and Atlanta Writings, 1983-1984 (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - "Landscape and Axiomatic", Undated (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - "Languor…", Undated (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - "Language and Structure", 1984 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - "Last Will and Testament", Undated (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - "Laura", Undated (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Laura Hayes "Breakthrough" 20 Minute Video Tape B/W, Undated (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - "Laurie Anderson: Procedure and Text", Undated (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - "Le Cinéma Sans Écran (Cinema Without the Screen)", 1980 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - "Left Hand, Right Hand", Undated (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - "Legwork", Undated (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - "Lesbian and Others Communities", Undated (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Letter From Rimbaud, from "Shortfilm" 1989, 20 Min., Undated (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - "Let Us Develop Literature and Art Suitable to the Encouragement of the Revolutionary Age", Undated (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - "The Lexicon as of August 10, 1989" (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - "Lies", Undated (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - "The Life of Woman in Man, The Life of Man in Woman", 1974 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - "Life Support", Undated (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - "The Line Holds Business Well For Other Things", Undated (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - "Lineal and Nonlineal Codifications of Reality", Undated (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - "Lines (For Sitting Across the Table From Each Other)", Undated (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - "Liquid", Undated (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - "Lists", 1971 (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - "Listening to A Side Joanless", Undated (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - "Literally Some Notes Towards the Work Surrounding Us", Undated (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - Literary Agencies - Documents, Undated (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - "Literary Pastiche of No Consequence (Motley Pastiche)", Undated (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - Literary Publishing - Documents, Undated (Box 43, Folder 27)
  - "Little Existentialist Poem", Undated (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - "Little German Poem", Undated (Box 43, Folder 29)
  - "Little Simple Romantic Poem: Country Fire", Undated (Box 43, Folder 30)
  - "Little Song", Undated (Box 43, Folder 31)
  - "The Location of the Mysteries", 1977 (Box 43, Folder 32)
  - "Location or the Speaking Of It", 1978 (Box 43, Folder 33)
  - "Locution", Undated (Box 43, Folder 34)
  - "The Logical Structure of Reality", Undated (Box 43, Folder 35)
  - "Logout/Fallout", Undated (Box 43, Folder 36)
  - "Loop/Loup", Undated (Box 43, Folder 37)
  - "Loop) or Without (Application of External Constraints)", Undated (Box 43, Folder 38)
  - "Los: A Magazine of Poetry", April, 1967 (Box 43, Folder 39)
  - "Losing", Undated (Box 43, Folder 40)
  - "Lou Lou", Undated (Box 43, Folder 41)
  - "Love", Undated (Box 43, Folder 42)
  - "Love and the Beginning of Language: Ideograms of the Body", Undated (Box 43, Folder 43)
  - "Love and Writing", Undated (Box 43, Folder 44)
  - "Loved", Undated (Box 43, Folder 45)
  - "Lunchtime", Undated (Box 43, Folder 46)
  - "Madness", Undated (Box 43, Folder 47)
  - "The Mad Writings of a Displaced Person", Undated (Box 43, Folder 48)
  - "Mapping", Undated (Box 43, Folder 49)
  - "Mappings (Here)", Undated (Box 43, Folder 50)
  - "Manifesto", Undated (Box 43, Folder 51)
  - "The Man of Desire", 1983 (Box 43, Folder 52)
  - "The Man Who Would Be Dog", Undated (Box 43, Folder 53)
  - "Marginalia (First Version, Indexical)", Undated (Box 43, Folder 54)
  - "Marginality", 1979 (Box 43, Folder 55)
  - Mathematical Writing, Undated (Box 44, Folder 1, 2, 3)
  - "Matter and Name", 1983 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - "Measurement and Substance", Undated (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - "Memorial", Undated (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - "Memory", Undated (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - "Memory of Childhood Domesticity", Undated (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - "Memory of Painting, Undated (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - "Men Without Women", Undated (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - "Metabody", 1993-1997 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_10)
    "Metabody" is a hybrid CD-ROM/Website with multimedia components.
  - Meta, Ltd., Undated (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - "Metal Stories", Undated (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - "Metasaga", Undated (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - "Metastructure for Bricklaying", Undated (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - "Mexican", Undated (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - "Mexico", Undated (Box 44, Folder 16, 17, 18, 19)
  - "Mindfuck", Undated (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - "Ministration", Undated (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - "Minox Piece", 1970 (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - "Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - "ML.TXT", Undated (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - "Model M", Undated (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - "Motherstructures", Undated (Box 44, Folder 26)
  - "Movie", Undated (Box 44, Folder 27)
  - "Movie Movie Movie", 1977 (Box 44, Folder 28)
  - "Moving Inward: Rewrite of a Computer Language Generation Program", 1978-1979 (Box 44, Folder 29)
  - "Mr. Jones Come Undone, Waiting in the Nightime Rain", Undated (Box 44, Folder 30)
  - Muck, 2004 (Box 44, Folder 31)
  - "My Future Work", Undated (Box 44, Folder 32)
  - "My Mouth Writing the Sucking of My Penis in This Heat My Writing, Undated (Box 44, Folder 33)
  - "Myth: Sources of Information", Undated (Box 44, Folder 34)
  - "My Theory", Undated (Box 44, Folder 35)
  - "Naivete", Undated (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Nancy Kitchell, 1967-1974 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - "The Narrows", Undated (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - "Nature and Discourse: 1975 Project" (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - "Nature of the Theoretical", Undated (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - "Near-Death: In Jhaptal", Undated (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - "Negation", Undated (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - "Negative Culture: Some Notes", Undated (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - "The Neoconservative Left", Undated (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - "Neologisms" Website by mIEKAL aND, 2001 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_11)
  - "Newport Chunk", Undated (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - "News-Space", Undated (Box 45, Folder 11)